Philipp Pisarevskiy

Skilled Product Designer

tel: +44 7935 146 787 +7 912 340 79 98

email: philipp@yoursdesigner.com

About me

I am a BA Product Design graduate from UAL, world's 6th art and design university, according to QS World University Rakings.

I've learnt and touched many different spheres of business and design over the last 5 years. But I always want to know more. I am looking for the next opportunity to expand and apply my superior range of skills and knowledge.

Skills and interests

Product, industrial design, R&D and production, presenting, prototyping and modelling.

Market & user research, analysis, trend forecasting, consulting, advertising and marketing.

CAD and class A modeling, CAM, mechanical engineering, design for manufacturing, technical specification.

Information technology, mathematics, applied science, machine learning, programming (Obj-C, C++/#, Swift, Python, PHP, JS, HTML, Matlab, Bash)

Software

CG 3ds max, Vray, Keyshot, 3D Coat, Substance Designer, HDR Light Studio, Maya, Houdini, Zbrush.

CAD Solidworks, Rhino, Grasshopper, Alias, CATIA, Siemens NX, Inventor.

2D Adobe Ps, Ai, Id, Ae, Pr, Dw, Corel.

Education

Central Saint Martins College of Art and Design

BA (Hons) Product Design, 1st Class Honours 2016 - 2018, London, UK

British Higher School Of Art And Design

BA (Hons) Product Design 2015 - 2016, Moscow, Russia

Awards

Red Dot Design Award 2021

Smart Product and Product Design, SberPortal

iF Design Award 2021

Discipline: Product, SberPortal

Central Saint Martins College of Art and Design

Foundation in Art and Design 2014 - 2015, London, UK

John Leggott College

A-levels in Further Maths, Design & Technology and Computing 2013 - 2014, Scunthorpe, UK

Competition finalist, design project for Zumtobel, 2017 London, UK

2nd **prize winner, design project for MTS Russia, 2016** Moscow, Russia

Experience

Designer, NotAnotherOne

2018 - present, Saint-Petersburg, Russia

Created and partly lead the design of a number of consumer devices in Russian market, starting from the market research and product specification, through to engineering and manufacturing support. Participated in the late-stage design for the own products that are sold worldwide, and other design-related activities in the company. The client list includes Sberbank, Yandex, Arrival, Megafon and more.

Co-Founder, Seamless

2016 - 2018, Moscow, Russia

Have been involved in building a retail experience startup, along with a team of an experienced IT entrepreneur and an economist. By December 2018, we have undertaken market and trend research, business planning, brand positioning and R&D work in data collection. Currently, switched to other projects.

Lead designer and consultant (contract), Ministry of Economics

2014 - 2016, Orenburg, Russia

Together with local government, developed a brand idenity for use in external and internal events. I was invited to work after a public competition, in which my work has taken the first prize, and after that, continued working on developing the brand and passing the guidelines to the design team on the client side.